<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DesignThinking</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="exe">Execute</string>
    <string name="title_user">About</string>
    <string name="learn">Learn the Concepts that drive design thinking.</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit your Project ideas around user innovations.</string>
    <string name="identify">Identify Customer needs and User groups.</string>
    <string name="four">Translate needs into product specifications.</string>
    <string name="five">Create a prototype.</string>
    <string name="six">Build out product architecture.</string>
    <string name="seven">Analyze the economics of the innovation. </string>
    <string name="eight">Choose the right development process.</string>
    <string name="nine">Present your final ideas, get real-time feedback.</string>

    <string name="week1">USER NEED \nINDENTIFICATION (EMPATHY)</string>
    <string name="week1s">The important element as well as first stage of design thinking to gain an empathetic understanding of people to solve the problem. </string>

    <string name="week2">DEFINE, IDEATION, AND PROTOTYPING</string>

    <string name="week2s">Define:- Put information together which created during emphathise stage.\nIdeation:- Get ready to start generating ideas.\nPrototyping:- The experimental phase to identify the best possible solution.</string>

    <string name="week3">TESTING PROTOTYPES AND FEEDBACK FROM USERS</string>
    <string name="week3s">The final stage of the five stage model but in an iterative process.</string>
    <string name="gal">Gallery</string>
    <string name="prj">Project</string>
    <string name="Prize">Prize</string>

    <string name="desc"> •	App and add-ons: An app for vending machines and additions required to implement it, it deals with IOT and machine to human interaction, the utility management of the machine and add-ons to implement the proposed idea.
    \n\n•	Models and prototype: Implementation and feasibility. Working prototype for the app.</string>

    <string name="dt2">1. Students will practice a design thinking process for innovation which can leads to some good
entrepreneurship ideas or projects.\n\n
2. It will help the students to get in touch with the real world problems.\n\n
3. Students will become familiar with the process of ideation followed by top institutes across the world.\n\n
4. Students will learn the techniques of prototyping their ideas.\n\n
        5. Students will learn how to find opportunities in the real world for entrepreneurship projects.\n\n
6. Students will be involved in collaborative and creative learning.\n
</string>


    <string name="dtt2">Design thinking is a framework for innovation. Most of the prestigious institutions like Stanford , Harvard and
top companies like SAP Google etc across the world follow this framework to create different products based
on their customers needs and requirements. This workshop will help the students to work on real world
problems and will make them familiar with the entire design thinking process. This workshop will also help the
students in generating different entrepreneurship ideas and also help them to think on it in a mature manner.
\n\nThis workshop will be followed by an idea presentation and prototyping challenge based on their 3 week effort.
The winner of this competition will get a prize. The prize will be decided later on as per the evaluation panel.</string>
</resources>
